wibmo.com 2017-12-04

# Privacy | Wibmo

Wibmo is committed to protecting your privacy. We have adopted privacy principles that are addressed in the following sections.

 **Type of information collected on wibmo.com**

 **Personal information**

Personal information is information that identifies you as an individual, such as your name, mailing address, email address, etc. Personal information is only obtained when you voluntarily provide the information to us. Wibmo uses personal information to better understand your needs and interests and to provide you with better service.  
Once you choose to provide us with personal information, you can be assured it will be used only for the intent it was collected for.

 **Non-personal information**

Non-personal information is information that does not identify you as an individual, such as your browser type, IP Address, the URL of the previous web site you visited, etc. Wibmo may automatically collect certain types of non-personal information from you when visiting wibmo.com. This helps us understand the usage of our site and demographics of our visitors.

 **External links**

Wibmo website (wibmo.com) may at times link to external websites. Wibmo is not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of those sites.

 **Acceptance of policy**

By visiting wibmo.com, you are accepting the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, and we have the right to use your information as described in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time and will post any changes on this page.

This Privacy Policy applies only with respect to the information that we collect on wibmo.com.

 **Wibmo respects your privacy and we are committed to protecting your personal information that you share with us.**
